David Adeola

London, England, United Kingdom



adeoladavidoluwole@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/david-adeola

Summary

Hi, I'm Adeola David, a Frontend Engineer with 4 years of experience building and maintaining web applications. Proficient in JavaScript, React, Next.js, TailwindCSS, Chakra UI, Postgresql, CSS, SCSS, Chrome DevTools, among other technologies.

Tech Stacks: JavaScript, React, Next.js, TailwindCSS, Postman, GitHub Actions

Databases: Firebase, Postgresql, MongoDB

Language: English

Experience



🛌 Frontend Engineer

unStack Africa

Jan 2021 - Present (1 year 3 months +)

Founder & Lead Engineer

OODA Solutions

May 2018 - Present (3 years 11 months +)

Frontend Web Developer

NIIT Lagos

Jun 2019 - Sep 2020 (1 year 4 months)

Frontend Developer

Orb Solutions Ltd

Apr 2016 - Feb 2017 (11 months)

I interned as a frontend developer was involved with the UI in the building of splashFm, where I worked alongside with my colleague Damilola Olorunsesan, and my Director Mr Ikenna, and my Boss Mr Bayo Akonde.

Education



Federal University Of Agriculture, Abeokuta

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science Sep 2018 - Sep 2023

Licenses & Certifications

HackerRank React development Assessment - HackerRank C5053E9F7B82

Skills

JavaScript • React.js • Web Applications • E-commerce • MongoDB • TypeScript • Node.js • Next.js • Webpack • Redux.js